Guide to the Men's Basketball Game Film Collection, 1947-1996 UA.13.01.0005
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Men's Basketball Game Films
  - Wake Forest, 1969 January 08
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 2, 1969 January 08; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 189, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0508)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 3, 1969 January 08; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 189, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0509)
  - Maryland, 1969 January 11
    Duke win; score: 96-85
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 1, 1969 January 11; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 185, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0510)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 2, 1969 January 11; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 185, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0511)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 3, 1969 January 11; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 185, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0512)
  - NC State, 1969 January 25
    Duke loss; score: 74-77
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 1, 1969 January 25; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 185, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0513)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 2, 1969 January 25; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 185, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0514)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 3, 1969 January 25; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 185, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0515)
  - South Carolina, 1969 February 08
    Duke loss; score: 72-82
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: Reel 1, 1969 February 08; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 185, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0516)
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: Reel 2, 1969 February 08; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 185, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0517)
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: Reel 3, 1969 February 08; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 185, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0518)
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: Reel 4, 1969 February 08; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 185, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0519)
  - Wake Forest, 1969 February 12
    Duke win; score: 122-93
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 1, 1969 February 12; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 186, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0520)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 2, 1969 February 12; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 186, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0521)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 3, 1969 February 12; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 186, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0522)
  - NC State, 1969 February 26
    Duke loss; score: 73-88
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 1, 1969 February 26; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 186, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0523)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 2, 1969 February 26; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 186, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0524)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 3, 1969 February 26; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 186, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0525)
  - North Carolina, 1969 March 01
    Duke win; score: 87-81
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 1, 1969 March 01; 16mm film: 14" reel (Box 195, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0529)
  - Virginia, 1969 March 06
    Duke win; score: 99-86
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Reel 1, 1969 March 06; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 186, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0530)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Reel 2, 1969 March 06; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 186, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0531)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Reel 3, 1969 March 06; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 186, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0532)
  - South Carolina, 1969 March 07
    Duke win; score: 68-59
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: Reel 1, 1969 March 07; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 186, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0533)
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: Reel 2, 1969 March 07; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 186, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0534)
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: Reel 3, 1969 March 07; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 186, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0535)
  - North Carolina, 1969 March 08
    Duke loss; score: 74-85
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 1, 1969 March 08; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 186, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0536)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 2, 1969 March 08; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 186, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0537)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 3, 1969 March 08; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 186, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0538)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 4, 1969 March 08; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 186, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0539)
  - Virginia Tech, 1969 December 01
    Duke win; score: 66-63
    - Duke vs. Virginia Tech: Reel 1, 1969 December 01; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 1, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0540)
    - Duke vs. Virginia Tech: Reel 2, 1969 December 01; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 1, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0541)
    - Duke vs. Virginia Tech: Reel 3, 1969 December 01; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 1, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0542)
    - Duke vs. Virginia Tech: Reel 4, 1969 December 01; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 1, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0543)
  - Virginia, 1969 December 06
    Duke win; score: 57-45
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Reel 1, 1969 December 06; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 1, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0544)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Reel 2, 1969 December 06; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 1, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0545)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Reel 3, 1969 December 06; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 1, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0546)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Reel 4, 1969 December 06; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 1, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0547)
  - Michigan, 1969 December 10
    Duke win; score: 73-68
    - Duke vs. Michigan: Reel 1, 1969 December 10; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 1, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0548)
    - Duke vs. Michigan: Reel 2, 1969 December 10; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 1, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0549)
  - NC State, 1969 December 13
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 1, 1969 December 13; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 1, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0552)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 2, 1969 December 13; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 1, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0553)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 3, 1969 December 13; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 1, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0554)
  - William & Mary, 1969 December 13
    - Duke vs. William & Mary: Reel 1, 1969 December 13; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 1, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0550)
    - Duke vs. William & Mary: Reel 2, 1969 December 13; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 1, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0551)
  - East Carolina, 1969 December 15
    Duke win; score: 80-65
    - Duke vs. East Carolina: Reel 1, 1969 December 15; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 1, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0555)
    - Duke vs. East Carolina: Reel 2, 1969 December 15; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 1, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0556)
    - Duke vs. East Carolina: Reel 3, 1969 December 15; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 1, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0557)
  - Dayton, 1969 December 19
    Duke win; score: 72-67
    - Duke vs. Dayton: Reel 1, 1969 December 19; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 2, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0558)
    - Duke vs. Dayton: Reel 2, 1969 December 19; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 2, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0559)
    - Duke vs. Dayton: Reel 3, 1969 December 19; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 2, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0560)
    - Duke vs. Dayton: Reel 4, 1969 December 19; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 2, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0561)
  - Kentucky, 1969 December 20
    Duke loss; score: 76-98
    - Duke vs. Kentucky: Reel 1, 1969 December 20; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 2, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0562)
    - Duke vs. Kentucky: Reel 2, 1969 December 20; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 2, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0563)
    - Duke vs. Kentucky: Reel 3, 1969 December 20; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 2, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0564)
    - Duke vs. Kentucky: Reel 4, 1969 December 20; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 2, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0565)
  - Wake Forest, 1969 December 23
    Duke win; score: 98-90
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 1, 1969 December 23; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 2, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0566)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 2, 1969 December 23; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 2, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0567)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 3, 1969 December 23; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 2, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0568)
  - Penn State, 1970 January 03
    Duke win; score: 93-43
    - Duke vs. Penn State: Reel 1, 1970 January 03; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 2, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0576)
    - Duke vs. Penn State: Reel 2, 1970 January 03; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 2, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0577)
  - Wake Forest, 1970 January 07
    Duke win; score: 78-72
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 1, 1970 January 07; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 2, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0578)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 2, 1970 January 07; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 2, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0579)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 3, 1970 January 07; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 2, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0580)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 4, 1970 January 07; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 2, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0581)
  - North Carolina, 1970 January 10
    Duke loss; score: 78-86
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 1, 1970 January 10; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 2, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0582)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 2, 1970 January 10; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 2, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0583)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 3, 1970 January 10; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 3, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0584)
  - NC State, 1970 January 24
    Duke loss; score: 76-77
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 1, 1970 January 24; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 3, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0585)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 2, 1970 January 24; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 3, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0586)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 3, 1970 January 24; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 3, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0587)
  - Maryland, 1970 January 28
    Duke loss; score: 50-52
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 1, 1970 January 28; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 3, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0588)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 2, 1970 January 28; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 3, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0589)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 3, 1970 January 28; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 3, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0590)
  - South Carolina, 1970 January 31
    Duke loss; score: 55-67
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: Reel 1, 1970 January 31; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 3, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0591)
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: Reel 2, 1970 January 31; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 3, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0592)
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: Reel 3, 1970 January 31; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 3, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0593)
  - West Virginia, 1970 February 07
    Duke win; score: 82-70
    - Duke vs. West Virginia: Reel 1, 1970 February 07; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 3, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0594)
    - Duke vs. West Virginia: Reel 2, 1970 February 07; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 3, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0595)
    - Duke vs. West Virginia: Reel 3, 1970 February 07; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 3, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0596)
  - Clemson, 1970 February 09
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Reel 1, 1970 February 09; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 3, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0597)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Reel 2, 1970 February 09; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 3, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0598)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Reel 3, 1970 February 09; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 3, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0599)
  - Wake Forest, 1970 February 11
    Duke win; score: 67-65
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 1, 1970 February 11; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 3, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0600)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 2, 1970 February 11; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 3, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0601)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 3, 1970 February 11; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 4, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0602)
  - South Carolina, 1970 February 14
    Duke loss; score: 65-82
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: Reel 1, 1970 February 14; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 4, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0603)
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: Reel 2, 1970 February 14; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 4, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0604)
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: Reel 3, 1970 February 14; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 4, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0605)
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: Reel 4, 1970 February 14; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 4, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0606)
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: Reel 5, 1970 February 14; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 4, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0607)
  - Davidson, 1970 February 18
    Duke win; score: 79-76
    - Duke vs. Davidson: Reel 1, 1970 February 18; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 4, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0608)
    - Duke vs. Davidson: Reel 2, 1970 February 18; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 4, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0609)
    - Duke vs. Davidson: Reel 3, 1970 February 18; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 4, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0610)
  - Maryland, 1970 February 21
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 1, 1970 February 21; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 4, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0611)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 2, 1970 February 21; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 4, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0612)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 3, 1970 February 21; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 4, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0613)
  - NC State, 1970 February 25
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 1, 1970 February 25; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 4, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0614)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 2, 1970 February 25; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 4, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0615)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 3, 1970 February 25; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 4, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0616)
  - North Carolina, 1970 February 28
    Duke win; score: 91-83
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 1, 1970 February 28; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 4, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0617)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 2, 1970 February 28; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 4, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0618)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 3, 1970 February 28; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 4, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0619)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 4, 1970 February 28; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 5, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0620)
  - Wake Forest, 1970 March 05
    Duke loss; score: 73-81
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 1, 1970 March 05; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 5, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0621)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 2, 1970 March 05; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 5, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0622)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 3, 1970 March 05; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 5, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0623)
  - Utah, 1970 March 14
    Duke loss; score: 75-78
    - Duke vs. Utah: Reel 1, 1970 March 14; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 164, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0624)
      Color print
  - Basketball Highlights of 1970, 1970 October 19
    - Basketball Highlights of 1970: Reel 1, 1970 October 19; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 164, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0625)
  - Basketball Highlights of 1970-1971 Season, circa 1970-1971
    - Basketball Highlights of 1970-1971 Season: Reel 1, circa 1970-1971; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 164, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0569)
    - Basketball Highlights of 1970-1971 Season: Reel 2, circa 1970-1971; 16mm film: 10" reel (Box 198, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0570)
    - Basketball Highlights of 1970-1971 Season: Reel 3, circa 1970-1971; 16mm film: 10" reel (Box 198, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0571)
    - Basketball Highlights of 1970-1971 Season: Opt. track, circa 1970-1971; 16mm film: 10" reel (Box 199, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0572)
    - Basketball Highlights of 1970-1971 Season: Opt. track, circa 1970-1971; 16mm film: 10" reel (Box 199, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0573)
    - Basketball Highlights of 1970-1971 Season: A roll, circa 1970-1971; 16mm film: 10" reel (Box 199, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0574)
    - Basketball Highlights of 1970-1971 Season: B roll, circa 1970-1971; 16mm film: 10" reel (Box 199, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0575)
  - North Carolina, 1970 November 21
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 1, 1970 November 21; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 6, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0626)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 2, 1970 November 21; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 6, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0627)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 3, 1970 November 21; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 6, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0628)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 4, 1970 November 21; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 6, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0629)
  - Princeton, 1970 December 02
    Duke win; score: 79-75; includes stats sheet
    - Duke vs. Princeton: Reel 1, 1970 December 02; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 5, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0630)
    - Duke vs. Princeton: Reel 2, 1970 December 02; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 5, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0631)
    - Duke vs. Princeton: Reel 3, 1970 December 02; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 5, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0632)
    - Duke vs. Princeton: Reel 4, 1970 December 02; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 5, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0633)
  - Virginia, 1970 December 05
    Duke loss; score: 70-75
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Reel 1, 1970 December 05; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 5, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0634)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Reel 2, 1970 December 05; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 5, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0635)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Reel 3, 1970 December 05; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 5, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0636)
  - Michigan, 1970 December 07
    Duke win; score: 95-74
    - Duke vs. Michigan: Reel 1, 1970 December 07; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 7, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0637)
    - Duke vs. Michigan: Reel 2, 1970 December 07; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 7, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0638)
    - Duke vs. Michigan: Reel 3, 1970 December 07; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 7, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0639)
    - Duke vs. Michigan: Reel 4, 1970 December 07; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 7, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0640)
  - North Carolina, 1970 December 09
    Duke loss; score 81-83
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 1, 1970 December 09; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 6, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0641)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 2, 1970 December 09; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 6, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0642)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 3, 1970 December 09; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 7, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0643)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 4, 1970 December 09; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 7, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0644)
  - South Carolina, 1970 December 12
    Duke loss; score: 78-98
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: Reel 1, 1970 December 12; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 5, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0645)
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: Reel 2, 1970 December 12; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 5, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0646)
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: Reel 3, 1970 December 12; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 5, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0647)
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: Reel 4, 1970 December 12; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 5, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0648)
    - Duke vs. South Carolina: Reel 5, 1970 December 12; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 5, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0649)
  - Virginia Tech, 1970 December 15
    Duke win; score: 104-75
    - Duke vs. Virginia Tech: Reel 1, 1970 December 15; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 5, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0650)
    - Duke vs. Virginia Tech: Reel 2, 1970 December 15; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 5, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0651)
    - Duke vs. Virginia Tech: Reel 3, 1970 December 15; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 5, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0652)
    - Duke vs. Virginia Tech: Reel 4, 1970 December 15; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 7, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0653)
  - Wake Forest, 1970 December 18
    Duke loss; score: 77-83
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 1, 1970 December 18; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 7, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0654)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 2, 1970 December 18; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 7, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0655)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 3, 1970 December 18; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 7, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0656)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 4, 1970 December 18; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 7, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0657)
  - North Carolina, 1970 December 19
    Duke loss; score: 81-83
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 1, 1970 December 19; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 6, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0658)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 2, 1970 December 19; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 6, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0659)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 3, 1970 December 19; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 6, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0660)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 4, 1970 December 19; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 6, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0661)
  - Dayton, 1970 December 22
    Duke win; score: 70-64
    - Duke vs. Dayton: Reel 1, 1970 December 22; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 7, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0662)
    - Duke vs. Dayton: Reel 2, 1970 December 22; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 7, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0663)
    - Duke vs. Dayton: Reel 3, 1970 December 22; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 7, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0664)
    - Duke vs. Dayton: Reel 4, 1970 December 22; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 7, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0665)
  - Santa Clara, 1971 December 27
    Duke win; score: 86-80
    - Duke vs. Santa Clara: Reel 1, 1971 December 27; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 6, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0666)
    - Duke vs. Santa Clara: Reel 2, 1971 December 27; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 6, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0667)
    - Duke vs. Santa Clara: Reel 3, 1971 December 27; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 6, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0668)
    - Duke vs. Santa Clara: Reel 4, 1971 December 27; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 6, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0669)
  - Northwestern, 1971 December 29
    Duke win; score: 93-87
    - Duke vs. Northwestern: Reel 1, 1971 December 29; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 6, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0670)
    - Duke vs. Northwestern: Reel 2, 1971 December 29; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 6, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0671)
    - Duke vs. Northwestern: Reel 3, 1971 December 29; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 6, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0672)
    - Duke vs. Northwestern: Reel 4, 1971 December 29; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 6, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0673)
  - Penn State, 1971 December 30
    Duke win; score: 67-56
    - Duke vs. Penn State: Reel 1, 1971 December 30; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 8, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0674)
    - Duke vs. Penn State: Reel 2, 1971 December 30; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 8, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0675)
    - Duke vs. Penn State: Reel 3, 1971 December 30; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 8, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0676)
  - Basketball Highlights, circa 1971
    Original Outtakes
    - Basketball Highlights: Reel 1, circa 1971; 16mm film: 10" reel (Box 199, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0677)
    - Basketball Highlights: Reel 2, circa 1971; 16mm film: 12" reel (Box 199, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0678)
  - Wake Forest, 1971 January 06
    Duke win; score: 68-67
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 1, 1971 January 06; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 7, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0679)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 2, 1971 January 06; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 7, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0680)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 3, 1971 January 06; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 7, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0681)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 4, 1971 January 06; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 7, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0682)
  - North Carolina, 1971 January 10
    Duke loss; score: 74-79
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 1, 1971 January 10; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 8, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0683)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 2, 1971 January 10; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 8, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0684)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 3, 1971 January 10; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 8, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0685)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 4, 1971 January 10; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 8, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0686)
  - NC State, 1971 January 13
    Duke loss; score: 89-93
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 1, 1971 January 13; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 11, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0687)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 2, 1971 January 13; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 11, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0688)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 3, 1971 January 13; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 11, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0689)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 4, 1971 January 13; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 11, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0690)
  - NC State, 1971 January 13
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 1, 1971 January 13; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 11, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0693)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 2, 1971 January 13; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 11, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0694)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 3, 1971 January 13; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 11, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0691)